Is he really the Godfather?
Why do you ask?
If he really is the
ruler of the Sovereign Sanctum...
why is House Carter
stuck ruling this tiny city?
Because Count Carter never respected him.
If you don't respect
a man like that…
he has no obligation
to make you powerful.
But, i-if he
really is the Godfather,
why would he be
digging in the mines?
The Godfather is still only human.
Even he needs rest.
I see.
Sandero,
never doubt a man who defeated you.
No one else on Golantis could do that.
The kind of power others kill
for…
probably means nothing to him.
Let’s go.
Clan Leader Ais sends
150,000 gold coins!
The Yale family sends
200,000 gold coins!
The Lord of Amberwater
City sends 200,000
gold coins and fifteen magic crystals!
It's gorgeous.
Absolutely.
Countess, your family really is...
pathetic.
The eldest son of
House Carter gets
married,
and there’s not
a single notable gift?
This is the Holy Cathedral!
Filthy peasants are not allowed!
We got an invitation!See?
They’re with me.
Let them through.
Roll with me.
How do we know he didn't steal it?
Ugh, he smells like a mine.
It's disgusting.
Severin, congrats, man!
I don’t have much,
but put
me down for three copper coins.
Same here. Three coppers from me.